Wow, what a beautiful array of coding.
Do you have any idea who wrote this?
Nope, no clue, I'm afraid.
Here's your team, Ms. Kobayashi.
Thanks, Selma, looks great.
Oh no, why are you staring at the code I wrote?
Is there something wrong with it?
No, actually, I was just saying, I really...
Wait, who wrote this again?
That would be me, miss.
And I can continue growing as well.
Call me shallow, but I just assumed you'd be serving tea forever.
What do you mean? You're the one who gave me all those books and told me to study!
I guess you would have high specs being a dragon. Great work, Elma.
This is amazing.
Oh no! Are you praising me, miss?
Yes, I am! This means we have another awesome fighting member on our team.
Way to go, Elma.
Thanks! All you have to do is leave it to me!
Great! Could you start by handling this, then?
And this? Oh, and this one, too.
And this. And this one, this one, this one, and this one.
We're counting on you!
Hold on! That's too much!
No, it's not. That's the amount of work you should be handling regularly.
Kobayashi's the one who's been dealing with your share of assignments up until this point,
while you were serving tea.
She already has way too much on her plate without covering for you.
Isn't that kind of incredible, Mr. Takuya?
Yes, it is. She is our pillar of strength.
Pillar?
Mm-hmm.
She's a pillar?
I see.
Miss Kobayashi, please stand up!
I challenge you to a duel!
Huh?
Come on! Let's fight fair and square!
Uh-huh.
Where is this coming from?
Maybe she's mad I gave her too much?
Well, yeah, that's how Elma is!
Huh.
I think I kind of understand how you feel when she comes after you.
She challenges me to the strangest matches, too.
There were these tests of strength, then seeing whose tail was longer, and even speed eating.
One time she challenged me to see which one of us could strip the clothes off of travelers first.
Wait, so you were partners in crime? Now it makes sense why you were playing together all the time. You're actually friends.
We are certainly not! Normally we would be trying to kill each other!
Miss Kobayashi, please be careful around Elma. Your gaze is as sharp as those in the Chaos Faction!
Is my resting face really that bad?
Hello! You showed! You didn't run! Great!
Well, I did consider taking some PTO. Can we please deal with this before we compete?
It's one of the limited-time sweets from the station. A soft, sweet pudding.
Normally this would be all it takes to satisfy Elma.
No! I'll have it when I win the match!
Whatever works.
The winner will be whoever completes the most of this work that hasn't been touched since who knows when.
All right!
You say it hasn't been touched yet, but someone has to be responsible for it, right?
Who?
Ah, that would be me.
I'm taking some time off. Going to Akibat with Fafnir.
See you later!
What a bastard. At least he works hard.
I honestly can't tell if you're upset or grateful from the lack of tone in your voice.
Shall we get started?
Uh, yeah.
Well, this might be the world's lamest competition.
Doesn't matter if I win or lose. The work gets done either way.
Time for lunch.
You feel like doing some ramen again?
Why don't you come with us, Elma?
No, thanks. I still have a lot to do.
Hmm. Beating a mere human like me can't possibly make you any happier, can it?
If I upset you, I sincerely apologize.
I'm not mad. And you shouldn't sell yourself short. Don't become a pillar, either.
A pillar?
That's right. I've watched way too many humans in despair become pillars in the other world.
What does that mean?
They support others by becoming a sacrifice themselves.
Human sacrifices?
The dragons of the Harmony Faction help humans, but many of my companions demand sacrifices in exchange.
Those people became human pillars and died. I couldn't stand it if that happened to you.
This conversation has taken an awfully dramatic turn.
I feel like we're losing you to your work. You have to stop sacrificing yourself and your happiness here.
The least you can do is allow me to lead the others.
Elma, could you bring your head closer, then close your eyes?
Huh? What do you mean?
Miss Kobayashi, please, you already have Toru.
But, um, if you want that from me too, I'm not one to tell you what to do.
Wake up!
Owens! Owens! Owens!
What the heck's the matter with you?
That's called an unnecessary concern.
What?
The world you live in now is different from the one you came from, so take some time to breathe.
Don't go thinking everything is the same.
There are no human sacrifices in modern Japan.
Also, I still have my honor as your senior here, so lay off my work.
I see.
I think we should go ahead and end this competition.
Yeah?
Kay.
I appreciate how concerned you were for me, though.
Thank you, Elma.
Sure.
Another day, another yen, am I right?
Okay, Elma.
You're coming with us to have drinks tonight.
Drinks?
Yeah, Takya's already standing by at our usual watering hole.
I bet it'll be fun to drink with everyone.
Uh, yeah.
And there are some things you can only talk about with liquid courage.
Now I'm excited!
And what's up with that outfit?
Ew!
You dragons really piss me off!
You think you can wear whatever you want?
Both!
You can't just wear glasses for fun.
Blindness is not a fashion statement!
No one's tits are that huge!
As one who wears glasses, I know there are big differences in sizes and frames.
If you're gonna wear them, you need to take a frame as I thought first.
I wanna go home.
Yeah!
This is a popular collaboration cafe.
We're pretty lucky it's emptier on weekdays.
Yeah.
Sorry for the wait.
Here's a special bonus illustrated coaster you ordered.
There are 15 types handed out at random.
I need you to be my partner in gathering stuff until I can collect them all.
Let's make it happen.
That's scary.
They're recruiting for patrols.
Yeah, they asked me if I wanted to work for them.
Huh?
They were impressed with my skills after they saw me catch that thief in the shopping district.
Right.
That actually happened, didn't it?
You think it would be safe?
Sweet of you to worry about me!
For others.
Oh, damn it!
Thanks so much for coming today, Toru.
You're in normal clothes.
What a surprise.
Miss Kobayashi said I should wear more than just my uniform.
So, um, how would you like me to patrol for you?
All you have to do is walk around the area and see if you spot anything strange.
It can be a little scary sometimes.
There's nothing in any of the worlds that can scare me!
I'm a chaos dragon born to be feared!
Oh, that's so cute.
Mrs. Sakibay, do you know any martial arts?
No, nothing at all.
So then you'd be a hindrance to me if something does happen.
Nothing is going to happen.
I promise this is one of the safest areas you could be in.
A red zone already?
Why today of all days?
Miss Sakibay, are you all right?
They're blocking the street and getting in the way, aren't they?
We should go warn them.
Maybe.
Hey, you guys!
You're disrupting the neighborhood by loitering here.
Oh, are we?
You got a problem with us?
I sure do.
What kind of species doesn't understand its own language?
Quit screwing around with me!
You idiot!
It lashes out way too fast!
I will only warn you one more time, so if you don't understand, then I will give up hope.
Go away.
You're going to recruit, picking a fight with us!
Team Dragon Buster's out!
That's the most obnoxious name I've ever heard.
So, let's regroup and get back to our patrol.
Do you know what you'll do if they come back for revenge?
Uh, yeah.
First, I'd make him.
That's the most suspicious person I've ever seen in my life!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You're skipping out on work, aren't you?
No, I got out early today.
Huh?
What's with that armband you're wearing?
I'm on patrol to maintain the peace for the neighborhood, of course.
Huh?
You are?
You're doing something to preserve the peace of the city we live in?
That's what I said.
Did I stutter?
Really?
I'm glad you finally found it for yourself.
You believe in justice!
Huh?
This is the best news!
From now on, you're in an agent of harmony!
I would be so honored to help you with your patrol!
I get the feeling you didn't understand what I said.
Oh, are you saying you'd like to take my place?
This is Saki-Ve!
I mean, you told me I'd be a hindrance, didn't you?
Oh, come on.
I'm a bit more experienced at detecting evil than you are.
You can ask me anything you want.
I'd like to know the fastest way to get rid of you.
Don't be embarrassed.
There are times you can be super cute.
So annoying.
I'd like to know what it is exactly that you consider evil.
I think it's okay to overlook some mild misconduct as long as it's not bothering anybody.
Well, there's a book of laws, right?
They shouldn't be doing anything against what's in there.
Hurry up!
It's about to turn red!
Hold it!
That's a traffic violation and a major fine to vote!
Prepare to be punished, you wicked villains!
Okay, okay.
Take a deep breath and lay off the kids.
What?
Are you defending evil?
I take it back, you are a chaos dragon!
Calm down.
If you're going to waste your time chasing after the little things, I'm going home.
And what was that about punishment?
Violence isn't going to solve anything.
Oh, sorry, Toru, but you're starting to sound a lot like Miss Kobayashi.
Really?
You mean it, Alma?
You get me, don't you?
I had a feeling you did.
Awkward.
You keep focusing on the little things because you're walking without purpose.
We must find the suspicious person.
So what do they look like?
Well, according to the flyer, they were dressed entirely in black and had long hair.
He's also described as a tall man with sharp eyes and glasses.
Oh, that sounds easy to identify.
It says here he was last seen dancing on the streets on his way to an elementary school.
I see.
So, kind of like that?
Yeah, exactly like that.
What is the meaning of this?
I was going over my choreography for an event with Takia.
Why do you have to do it out here?
Because our room is too small.
Try to remember you're a fearsome dragon and do your best to avoid suspicious behavior.
She's right, Faf.
You need to be more self-aware.
And you too?
We're patrolling the streets.
Excellent work.
A chaos faction and a harmony faction member working together in a world that seems determined
to drive everyone in it crazy.
Yet you seem to be the only one here bothered by it.
And save the lectures about being too influenced.
You're wrong.
Lately, I feel like I understand you, but I still think it's enormously dangerous here.
The common sense of this world doesn't completely mesh with our understanding.
It's not how we were created.
Never forget that.
Isn't it our differences that make living here so fun?
I found you!
Oh, you thought you were going to get away with that stunt, didn't you?
You seem like you could hold your own, but maybe not while he's here.
The strongest local delinquent.
They call him the Dragon of Destruction.
A woman, huh?
I always say if you can put up a fight, it doesn't matter what your gender is.
But if you can't fight, then I suggest you hurry up and apologize for wasting my time.
Do you still think you can fight me?
I hope you're not expecting any mercy!
There are way too many of them.
I guess I'll wear the dirty clothes Ms. Kobayashi gave me.
If you don't understand by now, then you never will!
You will never oppose me again!
Will you shut up?
Hmm?
Good afternoon, Toru. You look lovely, Ms. Toru.
Okay.
You sure are popular today. What's up?
Hey, Ryu, it's pretty late. Let's get out of here.
You expect me to take being defeated lying down?
I'll build my strength till I can get my revenge!
Sounds good!
There's a bear!
Perfect! Now you'll see how strong I've become!
I want to go to an amusement park!
I've never understood those places where people pay to stand in line all day just to make themselves throw up.
Have you not been to an amusement park, Ms. Kobayashi?
If that's the case, then I don't mind going with Kana and we can tell you all about it.
Suddenly a dragon's going to mentor me on the way this world works? Yeah, no.
I'll take you just this once, but only because I know so much about them.
And you're wanting to learn!
Can Psycho Replace come with us, too?
Why not?
Well, we're here.
What is this place?
It's hard to believe we're in the same country.
Right? So this is the kind of place it is.
Huh?
Every time I come here!
And therefore, when you encounter the unusual, you create fond memories for life.
Just allow yourself to let go and forget your daily routines.
I recognize that voice!
Me too.
Hello! I am your guide to this wacky world of dreams.
In a way, this job could be considered a type of parlor maid.
You don't think that's stretching it just a bit?
Working?
My father's friend runs this park and said they were kind of short-staffed.
So I'm helping him out.
Look at this.
If you're hungry, there's a cafe in this area here that I think you'd really enjoy.
Yeah? Thanks. We'll try it.
Hello! I am Parkourland's Akro!
Such a passionate employee.
Kobayashi, I'm gonna go play with Saikawai and Ilulu.
Okay. Meet back up at the Ferris wheel at four o'clock.
All right. What do you want to do?
I mean, just as adults all alone.
Can't imagine what you'd want to do with that, but I'm intrigued.
Huh. It's an entire room made out of mirrors.
Weird. There are way too many means.
What is the purpose of having mirrors covering every inch of the walls?
The better to re-examine and re-evaluate your truest self, my dear.
I see.
I wonder if it's telling me that I'm supposed to accept my human form as my truest self.
I have to say, you're conquering the maze pretty quickly.
I can usually tell the way from the echoes of sound.
You're kind of like a bat.
I've come to curse you!
I'm scared of costumes and props!
Calm down, Saikawa. I'll protect you.
I know this one. You spin the table.
Huh?
I'm trying to figure out why this is fun.
It's called centrifugal force?
Are you saying that humans enjoy physically experiencing a stronger rotational force
in order to become more aware of the planet's natural rotation?
Centrifugal force and rotational force aren't...
You know what? Let's go with that.
Yes.
Let's go with what?
Can I try spinning us around now?
Yeah, sure.
Here we go!
What is this?
How do we play with it?
Yarn, this is so fun!
The rock is spinning!
Sorry. I didn't mean to do it again.
Man, Psycho, you're pretty funny.
This, too, is a maid's duty.
A unicorn, huh?
They're notorious for falling in love with virgins.
Wow, are you saying this could be my moment?
Don't joke about that. Your virginity belongs to me.
Creepy.
Would you like a snack?
Lucky!
Yes, thank you very much!
Taco, is yours yummy, too?
Oh, but I forgot to save you some.
Sorry, Khan, I ate it all.
You're right, that one's yummy, too.
Wow, she held it back.
I can show self-control when it really counts.
Well, in that case, take this.
One more, please.
I had so much fun, Miss Kobayashi!
I couldn't tell through all your complaining.
As long as I'm with you, I'd have fun even in the depths of the darkest abyss where light can't reach!
That doesn't sound like fun to me, Toru.
But I guess I agree that fun is more about who you're with than where you are.
And you had fun with me, didn't you, Miss Kobayashi? Admit it!
I think the cafe Georgie mentioned should be around here somewhere.
I know that outfit!
That's the Victorian main style you told me you always admired since you were little!
That's the best smile I've seen on her at any place we went today!
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Georgie.
I mean, it tastes average.
Not like I have anyone to drink it with, you know?
I would think you'd drink it with me, wouldn't you?
They're here somewhere.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Choking up my own happiness, I guess.
Georgie!
You young ladies look like you're having fun.
I can send you copies of the sweet photos I just took of you.
I want to see now.
Kobayashi, you're late!
I'm so sorry.
We lost track of time.
So, shall we ride the Ferris wheel together?
Did Georgie take all these photos?
We were screaming because we were having a good time.
I would love to live in a place that was always so much fun!
Yeah, sorry my place is so ordinary and boring.
What's the matter, Toru?
I was just thinking about the rides.
Ones that make sharp turns and rock back and forth make me nervous.
Then there are the buildings with detailed designs and mascots modeled after fantastical beasts.
She's feeling nostalgic?
Wait a sec.
We're in a simulator!
Does it feel like riding a dragon?
Ugh.
Are they making these things to avoid riding dragons in real life?
You and their disgusting monsters!
How did you even jump to that interpretation?
If you'd love me to take you everywhere, it'd be like going to your personal amusement park every day!
That only has roller coasters!
Although, maybe...
Maybe I could do something like this every now and then.
Nah, it's not good for the hips.
Nye!
Nye?
Georgie!
Oh, hi!
Good morning to you ladies!
What the...
Did you forget your own name just now?
Hm?
Hi, Kanda's mom!
I brought you the photos from the amusement park.
There are thousands!
Wow, that's a lot.
It is? Then I'll go through all of them
and only show you the best ones.
Still a lot. Don't worry about it.
I'm sure they're all amazing.
This week on Who's Run?
Pisces!